<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MotionLayoutSample</string>

    <string name="pink_floyd">Pink Floyd</string>
    <string name="pink_floyd_tags">Psychedelic/Garage, Progressive Rock, Art Rock, Hard Rock</string>
    <string name="pink_floyd_short_description">Pink Floyd were an English rock band formed
        in London in 1965. Gaining a following as a psychedelic band, they were distinguished
        for their extended compositions, sonic experimentation, philosophical lyrics and elaborate
        live shows, and became a leading band of the progressive rock genre. They are one of the
        most commercially successful and influential groups in popular music history.</string>
    <string name="pink_floyd_about">Pink Floyd were founded by students Syd Barrett
        (guitar and lead vocals), Nick Mason (drums), Roger Waters (bass and vocals),
        and Richard Wright (keyboards and vocals). Under Barrett\'s leadership, they released two
        charting singles and a successful debut album, The Piper at the Gates of Dawn (1967).
        \n\nGuitarist and vocalist David Gilmour joined in December 1967; Barrett left in April 1968
        due to deteriorating mental health. Waters became their primary lyricist and thematic
        leader, devising the concepts behind the albums The Dark Side of the Moon (1973),
        Wish You Were Here (1975), Animals (1977), The Wall (1979) and The Final Cut (1983).
        The band also composed several film scores.</string>

    <string name="boc">Blue Öyster Cult</string>
    <string name="boc_tags">Hard Rock, Heavy Metal, Album Rock</string>
    <string name="boc_short_description">Blue Öyster Cult (often abbreviated BÖC or BOC) is
        an American rock band formed on Long Island, New York, in 1967, whose most successful
        work includes the hard rock songs "(Don't Fear) The Reaper," "Godzilla," "Black Blade,"
        "Burnin' for You" and "Shooting Shark."</string>
    <string name="boc_about">Blue Öyster Cult has sold more than 24 million records worldwide,
        including 7 million in the United States alone. The band\'s music videos, especially
        "Burnin' for You," received heavy rotation on MTV when the music television network
        premiered in 1981, cementing the band\'s contribution to the development and success of
        the music video in modern popular culture.\n\nWhile Blue Öyster Cult has been noted
        for heavy rock, they would often add their own
        tongue-in-cheek style. Keeping with their image, the band would often include
        out-of-context fragments of Pearlman’s The Soft Doctrines of Imaginos into their lyrics,
        giving their songs cryptic meanings. Additionally, the band would keep a folder
        of Meltzer\'s and Pearlman\'s word associations to insert into their music.</string>

    <string name="camel">Camel</string>
    <string name="camel_tags">Progressive Rock, Art Rock</string>
    <string name="camel_short_description">The band played is an English progressive rock group from London,
        England, United Kingdom. They formed circa 1964 when brothers Andrew and Ian Latimer got
        together with their respective friends Alan Butcher and Richard Over to form The
        Phantom Four.</string>
    <string name="camel_about">Camel played extensively around their home town of Guildford,
        Surrey before changing their name to Strange Brew. The group performed mainly cover tunes
        until mid-1968 when Ian Latimer quit to get married. Andrew Latimer and Alan Butcher placed
        an ad in the Surrey Advertiser for a bass player to which Doug Ferguson responded.
        \n\nOn 13th November 1968 Ferguson arrived for an audition and promptly impressed the duo with
        his confidence, a \'fat\' bass sound, excellent gear (Fender jazz bass, 2 Vox T-60 cabs with
        amps) and his own roadie! He was offered the gig on the spot. The new blues orientated
        trio was called The Brew. Shortly after joining The Brew, Ferguson told Latimer about an
        exciting drummer he knew. Andy Ward joined The Brew at the tender age of 14 and the heart
        of camel had begun to take shape.</string>

    <string name="king_crimson">King Crimson</string>
    <string name="king_crimson_tags">Progressive Rock, Art Rock, Album Rock</string>
    <string name="king_crimson_short_description">King Crimson are a progressive rock group from
        London, England, United Kingdom formed in 1968 by guitarist Robert Fripp and drummer
        Michael Giles. Though originally an all-British musical group, later members have included
        a number of Americans, most notably Adrian Belew, and Tony Levin. The name "King Crimson"
        was coined by Peter Sinfield as a synonym for Beelzebub, prince of demons.</string>
    <string name="king_crimson_about">King Crimson\'s debut album was In the Court of the Crimson
        King. The first major success of the new genre of progressive rock, many bands that would
        come to dominate \'prog\' in the 1970s first sought to emulate In the Court of the
        Crimson King, including Genesis, the Alan Parsons Project, and later Rush.
The line-up of King Crimson has at times changed drastically from album to album.</string>

</resources>